<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mingfei's Blog</title><link>https://mingfei.io/</link><description>Recent content on Mingfei's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mingfei.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 1: 03/25 - 03/31</title><link>https://mingfei.io/weekly-updates/week1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mingfei.io/weekly-updates/week1/</guid><description>Highlight: made a blog post about my sabbatical plan I pretty much stopped sharing online after becoming a manager. Initially I thought it was because of lack of motivation – meetings seemed to have sucked up all my desire for expression, and I didn’t bother to get stuff cleared by comms. Later I realized that it was really imposter syndrome that held me back the most – I was worried that I’d say something dumb and all my colleagues and reports would notice and think I&amp;rsquo;m an idiot.</description></item><item><title>Leaving Facebook/Meta</title><link>https://mingfei.io/blog/leaving-fb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mingfei.io/blog/leaving-fb/</guid><description>I left Facebook/Meta on Friday.
When I joined Facebook 11 years ago, I was just hoping to work with cool hackers for a few years, experience the Silicon Valley tech scene, make some money, and then go back to school to continue my theoretical computer science research. I soon became obsessed with the impact I got to make on billions of people, the coworkers I got to collaborate with and learn from, and the new skills and mindset shifts I got to pick up every day.</description></item><item><title>Google Cloud setup for deep learning</title><link>https://mingfei.io/blog/gcp-setup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mingfei.io/blog/gcp-setup/</guid><description>Introduction Unlike most deep learning courses that teach you the core concepts based on toy examples, the course I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking recently, Deep Learning Fundametals, gets you hands-on with the latest open-source tools for training real-world deep learning models. While this sounds exciting, it does demand more than the conventional Google Colab / Macbook development environments can offer – without some serious GPU power, it takes forever to train a ResNet-50 from scratch or fine tune all parameters of a DistilBert model.</description></item></channel></rss>